<case10>
    <case10-1>
        <question>A father brings his daughter who is suffering from diarrhoea into the clinic. With this initial information, what are your next steps?
        </question>
        <answers>
            <label>
            1.	Check to see if the child is unconscious or lethargic?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            2.	Ask if the child has a history of asthma?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>Respiratory symptoms and questions are reviewed later.
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            3.	Check to see if the child has sunken eyes?  
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            4.	Determine if the child is older than 1 year?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>You must first determine if the child is dehydrated before addressing symptoms of dysentery.                   </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            5.	Check to see if the child is unable to drink or is drinking poorly?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            6.	Ask if the child has had diarrhoea for longer than 14 days?  
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>	You must first determine if the child is dehydrated before addressing symptoms of diarrhoea.
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            7.	Check to see if the child is breathing fast?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>Respiratory symptoms and questions are reviewed later.
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            8.	Check to see if the skin pinch goes back very slowly (>2 seconds)?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
        </answers>
        <correct_feedback>Correct! The next steps are: Unconscious/lethargic? Unable/drinking poorly? Sunken eyes?
        </correct_feedback>
    </case10-1>
    <case10-2>
        <question>You are given the answers to these questions as follows: No, No, No, and No. Based on this information, what are your next steps? Check all that apply
        </question>
        <answers>
            <label>
            1.	Check to see if the child is restless or irritable?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            2.	Check to see if the child drinks eagerly or is thirsty?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            3.	Diagnose as severe dehydration?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>The child did not have at least 2 of the previous symptoms that you asked about. The child does not have severe dehydration.                  
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            4.	Ask if there is blood in the stool?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>You must determine if the child is dehydrated before assessing the symptoms of dysentery.                  
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            5.	Ask if the child has had diarrhoea for longer than 14 days?
                
                <incorrect_str>You must determine if the child is dehydrated before assessing the symptoms of diarrhoea.                  
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            6.	Check to see if the child has sunken eyes? 
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            7.	Diagnose as dysentery?
                
                <correct_val>false</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str>You do not have sufficient information to diagnose the child with dysentery.
                </incorrect_str>
            </label>
            <label>
            8.	Check to see if the skin pinch goes back slowly (2 seconds)?
                
                <correct_val>true</correct_val>
                <incorrect_str></incorrect_str>
            </label>
        </answers>
        <correct_feedback>Correct! The next steps are: Restless/Irritable? Thirsty/drinking eagerly? Sunken eyes? Skin pinch goes back slowly?
        </correct_feedback>
    </case10-2>
</case10>